I just want to say I'm really proud of how my audience treats my guests when they come
on Views from Amanda Land.
They are just warm and welcoming and inquisitive and curious and compassionate and classy.
And so for all of you all who watch Views from Amanda Land on Wednesdays live, I just
want to send out some love to you guys because you really make it such an incredible environment.
And I've had many times where people who have come on the show will come back and be like,
oh, wow, you know, there was so much kindness in the comments.
I'm like, yeah, because that's the environment that has been fostered here.
And so much of that is simply because that's how y'all show up every week.
So shout out to the Amanda Landers.
And I can't wait to have that same good vibe energy at the Amanda Land Summit in September.
Amen.